You don't know the real story.
Annabelle: Creation is a horror film directed by David F. Sandberg.
Several years after the tragic death of their little girl, a doll maker and his wife welcome a nun and several girls from a
shuttered orphanage into their home, soon becoming the target of the doll maker's possessed creation—Annabelle.
Sister Charlotte, played by Stephanie Sigman.
Janice, played by Talitha Eliana Bateman.
Linda, played by Lulu Wilson.
Samuel Mullins, played by Anthony LaPaglia.
Esther Mullins, played by Miranda Otto.
Carol, played by Grace Caroline Currey.
Annabelle: Creation is a 2017 American supernatural
horror film directed by David F.
Sandberg, written by Gary Dauberman and produced by Peter Safran and James Wan.
It is a prequel to 2014's Annabelle and the fourth
installment in The Conjuring Universe franchise.
The film stars Stephanie Sigman, Talitha Bateman, Lulu Wilson, Anthony LaPaglia,
and Miranda Otto, and depicts the possessed Annabelle doll's origin.
In October 2015, it was confirmed that an Annabelle sequel was in development; it was
later revealed that the film would be a prequel rather than a sequel.
Lights Out director David F.
Sandberg replaced John R.
Leonetti as director, with Dauberman returning to write the
script and Safran and Wan returning to produce.
Principal photography began on June 27, 2016, in Los Angeles,
California, and concluded on August 15, 2016.
Annabelle: Creation premiered at the LA Film Festival on June 19, 2017, and was
theatrically released in the United States on August 11, 2017.
The film grossed over $306 million worldwide and received
generally positive reviews from critics.
A sequel, Annabelle Comes Home, was released on June 26, 2019.
The film explores themes of halloween, prequel, evil doll, demon, spin off.
The tone is dark.